rapidrepair.com 2010-12-29

# Rapid Repair - Links | iPod Repair, iPhone Repair, Batteries, LCD Screens and more | Fast iPod Repair, iPhone Repair and Zune Repair | Fast iPod Repair, iPhone Repair and Zune Repair

**Rapid Repair Privacy Policy**

* * *

##  [ ](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.rapidrepair.com&sealid=101)

**_Orders_**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

 When you place an order, we will typically contact you in this order;

-         e-mail order confirmation 

-         receipt notification (if you are shipping an item in for repair)

-         quote ready or contact us e-mail (if you are shipping an item in for repair)

-         verify contact has been made and we have authorization for further action

-         shipping notification

 We may contact you via phone or e-mail for any one of the steps listed above.  We may also contact you if we have trouble processing your order during any one of these steps. There will be a 15% restocking fee for all parts and devices that are returned in fully functional order.

_Uses of Information_

Rapid Repair collects certain personally identifiable information and other secure personal data (e.g. Credit Card Data.)  Rapid Repair uses this information in the filling or servicing of your order.  We typically use this information to verify the authenticity and authority for any credit card presented for payment and to contact users regarding their order or item in for service. 

 To protect your personally-identifiable information, data is transmitted via a secure connection to our servers, and is kept in an encrypted, protected database.  This information is available only to Rapid Repair and its employees and only for the purposes necessary in the normal operation of conducting business.  We DO NOT sell or share this information with any third parties.

 We also collect other non-personally identifying information, detailed below in the Information Sharing section below.

Communications from the Site

_Special Offers and Updates_

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.” 

_Customer Service_

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your information.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your order. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

Our Address info: 

Rapid Repair  
2328 Winters Dr.  
Portage, MI 49002  
(Please do NOT mail in an iPod without placing an order online first.)

_Rush Processing_

RapidRepair.com offers rush processing for orders placed before before 12PM EST for a small additional fee. The billing and shipping information must be the same. RapidRepair will make a strong effort to ship the order the same day (for self installed parts) and rush repairs (for mail in device repairs) but we cannot guarantee the order will ship same day even with this fee. If we fail to ship the order out on the same day, we will refund the rush processing fee. This rush processing fee is non-refundable for mail in repair orders (in-house diagnostics & repairs). 

Rush Processing is only available if the following conditions are met:

  * Billing address and shipping address are accurate and verified.
  * If parts are in stock(99% of items will be available)
  * Order is placed before the shipping deadline.

***Not valid for self installed parts when paying with a check, money order, or PayPal.  
***Valid Monday through Friday only, Saturday and Sunday we do not ship orders.  
***Holidays are also excluded for this offer.  
***Shipping deadline for any business day is 3PM EST.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.  This information does not identify individual users. 

 We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information

_  Personally identifiable information:_

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

  _Legal Disclaimer_

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, delete or deactivate it] by emailing us, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed on our  policies pages.

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  To learn more about SSL, follow this  [ link](http://www.rapidssl.com/resources/siteseal/rapid-ssl.html).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

Affiliates

If you wish to join our affiliate program, we collect personally identifiable information such as Name, E-mail, phone, and address. Your information will be used for the sole purpose of communication between  Rapid Repair and the affiliate. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at:

**Choice/Opt-out**

 If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at 

**Log Files**

 As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. 

 We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

 We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

 We use a third-party tracking service, called Google Ad Words conversion tracking that uses cookies [log files] to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate.  This is typically used to capture usage and volume statistics, page use, and to track conversion rates of visitors especially by source.

**Cookies**  

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site.  We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and to let us know what our visitors are interested in.  A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.  You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.  

We set a persistent cookie to store your shopping basket, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.   

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some functions of our site, such as the shopping basket, will be limited.  Cookies are used to store which items have been added to your basket and the ability to re-open the site at a later time with the same basket contents.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

** Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)** 

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages or e-mail and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.” 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Rapid Repair LLC. Please be aware that we, Rapid Repair, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.   

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**Credit Card Processing**

We use other third parties to provide credit card processing on our site.  When you place an order using a credit card, we will share: address, credit details, and your email address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

Required Disclosure:

Rapid Repair is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the site www.RapidRepair.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Service.  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at  [ _http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php_](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php).  TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

>
